# Alessio Palumbo

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

I am a Junior Web Developer who recently joined the community attracted by the opportunity to solve people's real problems at a global scale. I am a dedicated member of the team who loves to learn new skills, works hard to get things done and gets along with everybody.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Coder Academy,** Melbourne, Vic — Bootcamper

August 2017 - March 2018

Html5, Css3, Javascript, Ruby, Rails, MEAN stack, React, Git

## Kodama Coffee, Williamstown, Vic — Head Chef

October 2016- July 2017

## **The Builders Arms Hotel, Fitzroy, Vic — Commis Chef**

February 2016 - October 2016

# **Three One 2 One**, Richmond, Vic — *Chef de Partie*

October 2014 - January 2016

## **Park Hyatt Hotel,** Melbourne, Vic — Commis Chef

January 2014 - March 2015

## **Coffea**, Melbourne, Vic — Chef Assistant

May 2013 - May 2014

# Pie Face Pty ltd, Melbourne, Vic — Team Leader

May 2012 - April 2013

## **CPO&Partners Co., Ltd.,** Shanghai — Assistant Manager

June 2010 - July 2011

Liaised with local suppliers and consultants, Processed orders, Market research, Prepared and Attended meetings, Answered calls and emails. Performed Interpreting and Translation, Quality control, Bookkeeping.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Ca' Foscari, Venice — Ba in Culture & Language Mediation

September 2006 - March 2010

Mandarin Chinese, English, Interpreting and Translation.

#### LINKS

alessio-palumbo.netlify.com github.com/alessio-palumbo linkedin.com/in/alessio-palumbo twitter.com/\_alessiopalumbo

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Instarails**

https://github.com/alessio-palu mbo/instarails RailsBnb https://github.com/alessio-palu mbo/rails\_bnb

mbo/rails\_bnb Smartgoals https://github.com/alessio-palu

mbo/smartgoals MyPortfolio

https://github.com/alessio-palumbo/my-portfolio

#### **WEB DEVELOPMENT SKILLS**

HTML5

CSS<sub>3</sub>

**Javascript** 

Ruby

**Rails** 

Git

**Figma** 

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Management

Leadership

Organization

Teamwork

**Customer Service** 

Creativity

#### **LANGUAGES**

Italian: Native
English: Fluent
Mandarin: Fluent